do you guys go to the gym I go to the gym but you already knew that but I don't
think I'll ever be as buff as this kangaroo
look at that oh my god he's like an alien
holy shit like he is jacked like has he been stacking do you even lift bra yes I'm
intimidated I feel like he's about to kick my ass like like yo bro I'll rip your head
off and stuff it in my pouch like a trophy motherfucker now the version you guys
sent me only has 12,000 views so unless there's another copy out there I think
this is fairly fresh look at that oh my god and I don't blame the cameraman for laughing
his ass off me how do you even get this buff yeah I've been bench pressing koala
bears all day you know I typically eat plants and berries but no trans fats you
know can you spot me you know it even seems like he's looking for an excuse to
flex like yep you should check out the other exhibits over there so this next
video is great it's really squirrel so this is someone's pet squirrel trying to
bury a nut in a dog's fur
oh I have nothing to say about this other than it's fucking cute and like it is
cute but he makes a serious attempt to cover up that nut yeah no one will think
to look here so I found this over on a blog I read sometimes called io9 and it
has four million views damn so it's blowing up and why do they have a pet
squirrel and like why isn't that dog murdering that squirrel look I'm not
saying the dog should murder the squirrel it's just all right I have four cats and
when they see a squirrel they're like
and if you look at the dog the dog just couldn't be more apathetic I mean he just
doesn't care he's like you know all those fucks I have to give I buried him in the
backyard if you're curious how the video ends it looks like the squirrel ends up
hiding his nuts in the laundry basket now high-speed chases will never not be
exciting but this is the first time I've ever seen one where the cop was
actually wearing a camera
this cop's actually not a traditional cop he's apparently part of the Arkansas
Game and Fish Commission so if you're thinking about fishing without a permit he
will fuck you up now the video gets unfortunately funny when the officer
catches the suspect who appears to be a total meth head
now this whole scene apparently went down back in August of 2012 and it's just
now blowing up either that or it's an elaborate commercial for Google Glass
see to me this is like the real-life Breaking Bad people fantasize about
living this Breaking Bad life but in reality that's what the real Jesse
Pinkman would look like now there's a lot of contention about how the
officer handled the arrest after the suspect got out of the car but you
know if you're on meth driving on the wrong side of the highway endangering
lives I'd say getting cursed at with a gun stuck to your neck it's a
possibility you know I kind of feel bad for the guy but it's like that with
80 percent of the videos that you send me it's like I feel bad for the
person but at the same time I'm like dude what the fuck were you
thinking see you know this guy he's busted he's gonna go to jail this will
probably be a cellmate do you even fuck bro and you know what else after
seeing this video I'm seriously having second thoughts about ever doing meth
but that's all my time guys I'll see you later in the week don't forget share
out the full videos links are down below in the description I'm Ray William
Johnson and I approve this message
yeah I've been bench pressing koala bears all day you know I typically
eat plants and berries but no trans fats you know can you spot me can you give me a spot
you spot can you spot can you spot over there just spot spot you spot me with
spot you spot him I'll spot you but it's spot on my wall and dog name spot
somebody not know how to flush the toilet after they've had a shit
oh it's you hey